CARLOS ARELLANO

2306-1477 Mississauga Valley Blvd Mississauga L5A 3Y4

Tel: 647-986-4001

Email: carlos arellano@hotmail.ca

POFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

5 years working in the IT field at Apple has allowed me to gain customer management, troubleshooting and team work skills needed to be able to work in the Web Development field.

8 years working in the customer service field has also taught me how to deal with multiple teams and all kinds of customer concerns. Always meeting deadlines, and providing feedback needed to my peers for their growth as well as my own.

Demonstrated composure, honesty and always have been able to deal with ambiguity during every interaction and every role performed.

EDUCATION

Humber College (2019)

Web Design and Development

Sheridan College (2018)

Computer Programming

Monsignor Fraser College, Isabella Campus, Toronto (2008 - 2010)

High School Graduate

CBTIS 133, Mexico City, Mexico (2005 - 2008)

Technical Career in Computers, High School Graduate

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Apple Canada-Genius (2014 - Present)

- Troubleshoot and repair both software and hardware in a timely manner.
- Facilitate one on one training to customer regarding Apple software and products.
- Maintaining both customer and company satisfaction through exceptional customer service.

- Visual merchandising and in store devices maintenance.
- Assist leadership with hiring and training of new employees.
- Implemented and trained a visual merchandising team that now has been expanded to other stores in the market.

Starbucks Barista-Shift Supervisor (2011 – 2015)

- Costumer service Provide beverages and food to costumers, address costumers' issues all in a timely manner.
- Cash management Balancing cash tills.
- Opening and closing store Morning inventory counts, balancing tills, creating orders of in store use products.
- Supervising employees Delegating breaks, positioning, store set ups, barista training.
- Inventory Daily and monthly counts, creating daily order of products needed for in store use.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Mennonite New Life Centre, Popular Theatre, Toronto: *Volunteer/Participant* (2008 - 2010)

- Perform outreach activities for the youth programs
- Organize outings and events

Sherbourne Health Centre: REACT, Anti-Oppression and Leadership Training (June 2009)

- Participated in peer education program made of dynamic and skilled youth who facilitate interactive workshops, trainings, and speaking engagements on violence.
- Received certificate of participation for youth preventing violence